A Guide to the Papers of Henry Evans Howell, Jr. 1948-1976
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University Libraries, Old Dominion University
- SERIES IV: LEGISLATIVE PAPERS
  - Sub-Series D: General Assembly Session 1966-1967
    - Banking (Interest Rates) Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1966 (Box-folder Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Civil Service Retirement Bill Correspondence, February - March, 1966 (Box-folder Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Consumer Affairs: Consumer Protection Agency, Utilities Regulation; Insurance Regulation, 1966 (Box-folder Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Consumer Affairs - Seaboard Railroad - I.C.C. Hearing - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, August-October, 1966 (Box-folder Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Education - General Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1966 (Box-folder Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Health and Welfare (General) Correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Industry - Tidewater - 1966 Industrial Directory, 1966 (Box-folder Box 139, Folder 3)
    - "Liquor-by-the-Drink" Correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Poll Tax - Correspondence; Newsclips, 1966 (Box-folder Box 139, Folder 5)
    - General, January, 1967 (Box-folder Box 139, Folder 6)
    - General, February, 1967 (Box-folder Box 139, Folder 7)
    - General, March, 1967 (Box-folder Box 139, Folder 8)
    - General, April, 1967 (Box-folder Box 139, Folder 9)
    - General, May, 1967 (Box-folder Box 139, Folder 10)
    - General, June, 1967 (Box-folder Box 139, Folder 11)
    - General, July, 1967 (Box-folder Box 139, Folder 12)
    - General, August, 1967 (Box-folder Box 140, Folder 1)
    - General, September, 1967 (Box-folder Box 140, Folder 2)
    - General, October, 1967 (Box-folder Box 140, Folder 3)
    - General, November, 1967 (Box-folder Box 140, Folder 4)
    - General, December 1-15, 1967 (Box-folder Box 140, Folder 5)
    - General, December 16-31, 1967 (Box-folder Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Auto Insurance - General Correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Auto Insurance - Complaints re: Cancellations -Correspondence, January-June, 1967 (Box-folder Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Auto Insurance - Complaints re: Cancellations -Correspondence, July-October, 1967 (Box-folder Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Auto Insurance - Complaints re: Cancellations -Correspondence, November-December, 1967 (Box-folder Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Auto insurance - Correspondence with George E. Allen, Jr., T. Grayson Maddrea, January-June, 1967 (Box-folder Box 140, Folder 11)
    - Auto insurance - Correspondence with George E. Allen, Jr., T. Grayson Maddrea, July-December, 1967 (Box-folder Box 140, Folder 12)
    - Auto Insurance - Correspondence with State Corporation Commission; Attorney General, 1967 (Box-folder Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Auto Insurance - Articles; Newspaper Clippings, 1967 (Box-folder Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Banking - Interest Rates - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, January-March, 1967 (Box-folder Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Conflict of Interest Bill - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1967 (Box-folder Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Consumer Affairs - Utilities Regulation: VEPCO, Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company; C & P, 1967 (Box-folder Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Consumer Affairs - Correspondence with Virginia Citizens Consumer Council, 1967 (Box-folder Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Consumer Protection Agency - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1967 (Box-folder Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Education (General) - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1967 (Box-folder Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Education - Mills Godwin Speeches (Texts), 1967 (Box-folder Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Education - Report of Higher Education Study Commission, January, 1967 (Box-folder Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Education (V.E.A.) - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1967 (Box-folder Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Health and Welfare (General) - Correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder Box 141, Folder 12)
    - Health and Welfare (HEW Report on Mental Health Activities), (1962), 1967 (Box-folder Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Health and Welfare (Miscellaneous Reports on Health Care in Virginia,1953-1967), 1967 (Box-folder Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Health and Welfare - Norfolk Mental Health Center, 1967 (Box-folder Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Health and Welfare - Transfer of Patients from Eastern State Hospital - Complaints, especially Norfolk, January-May, 1967 (Box-folder Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Health and Welfare - Transfer of Patients from Eastern State Hospital - Correspondence: Complaints, especially from Norfolk, June-December, 1967 (Box-folder Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Health and Welfare - Transfer of Patients from Eastern State Hospital- Correspondence with Department of Mental Hygiene and Hospitals, March-April, 1967 (Box-folder Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Health and Welfare - Transfer of Patients from Eastern State Hospital -Correspondence with Department of Mental Hygiene and Hospitals, May-November, 1967 (Box-folder Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Health and Welfare - Transfer of Patients from Eastern State Hospital - Correspondence re: Political Action, 1967 (Box-folder Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Health and Welfare - Virginia Department of Mental Hygiene and Hospitals - Correspondence (General), 1967 (Box-folder Box 142, Folder 9)
    - "Liquor-by-the-Drink" - Correspondence, August, 1967 (Box-folder Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Metropolitan Government - Miscellaneous Studies, 1967 (Box-folder Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Ports - Tidewater Area - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1967 (Box-folder Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Ports - Virginia - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1967 (Box-folder Box 142, Folder 13)
    - Salt Water Sport Fishing - Correspondence, March-September, 1967 (Box-folder Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Workmen's Compensation - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1967 (Box-folder Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series E: General Assembly Session 1968-1969
    - General, January 1-15, 1968 (Box-folder Box 143, Folder 3)
    - General, January 16-31, 1968 (Box-folder Box 143, Folder 4)
    - General, February, 1968 (Box-folder Box 143, Folder 5)
    - General, March 1-20, 1968 (Box-folder Box 143, Folder 6)
    - General, March 21-31, 1968 (Box-folder Box 143, Folder 7)
    - General, April, 1968 (Box-folder Box 143, Folder 8)
    - General, May, 1968 (Box-folder Box 143, Folder 9)
    - General, June-September, 1968 (Box-folder Box 143, Folder 10)
    - General, October-November, 1968 (Box-folder Box 143, Folder 11)
    - General, December, 1968 (Box-folder Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Auto Insurance (General) - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1968 (Box-folder Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Auto Insurance - Complaints re: Cancellations - Correspondence, 1968 (Box-folder Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Auto Insurance - S.C.C. Correspondence (largely copies of George Allen, Jr., correspondence), 1968 (Box-folder Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Auto Insurance - Habitual Offender Bill Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box-folder Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Auto Insurance: Howell-Sacks Bill - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1967-1968 (Box-folder Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Conflict of Interest Bill - Miscellaneous Material, January-February, 1968 (Box-folder Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Consumer Protection - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, January-August, 1968 (Box-folder Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Education (General) Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, January, 1968 (Box-folder Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Education (General) Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, February-June, 1968 (Box-folder Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Education (Howell Criticism of Norfolk Schools) Correspondence, February-May, 1968 (Box-folder Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Education - Old Dominion University - Data re: Budget Requests, 1967-1968 (Box-folder Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Education - Virginia Institute of Marine Science - Data re: Budget Requests, 1967-1968 (Box-folder Box 144, Folder 12)
    - Equal Opportunity Commission - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1967-1968 (Box-folder Box 144, Folder 13)
    - Garnishment Bill - Miscellaneous Material, 1968 (Box-folder Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Handicapped Children - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1967-1968 (Box-folder Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Health and Welfare (General) - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1968 (Box-folder Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Health and Welfare (Transfer of Mental Patients to Central State Hospital) - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1968 (Box-folder Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Health and Welfare - Department of Mental Hygiene and Hospitals Annual Reports - 1967-1968; 1950-1951 (Box-folder Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Health and Welfare - Department of Mental Hygiene and Hospitals - "Mental Health in Virginia" - Miscellaneous Issues, 1968 (Box-folder Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Highways - Virginia Allocation of Funds, April, 1968 (Box-folder Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Income Tax Study Commission (Virginia) - "Toward a Simplified Income Tax System for Virginia Taxpayers," 1968 (Box-folder Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Interest Rates - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1967-1968 (Box-folder Box 145, Folder 9)
    - "Liquor-by-the-Drink" - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1968 (Box-folder Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Metropolitan Government - Hampton Roads - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, January-February, 1968 (Box-folder Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Truck Trailer Regulations (Senate Bill #1) - Correspondence, January-February, 1968 (Box-folder Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Right-to-Work Bill - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1967-1968 (Box-folder Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Right-to-Work Bill - Miscellaneous Materials, 1964-1968 (Box-folder Box 145, Folder 14)
    - Workmen's Compensation - Miscellaneous Material, January- February, 1968 (Box-folder Box 145, Folder 15)
    - General, January, 1969 (Box-folder Box 146, Folder 1)
    - General, February, 1969 (Box-folder Box 146, Folder 2)
    - General, March, 1969 (Box-folder Box 146, Folder 3)
    - General, April, 1969 (Box-folder Box 146, Folder 4)
    - General, May, 1969 (Box-folder Box 146, Folder 5)
    - General, June, 1969 (Box-folder Box 146, Folder 6)
    - General, July, 1969 (Box-folder Box 146, Folder 7)
    - General, August, 1969 (Box-folder Box 146, Folder 8)
    - General, September-December, 1969 (Box-folder Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Auto Insurance - General Miscellaneous Material, 1969 (Box-folder Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Auto Insurance - Correspondence re: Cancellation Complaints, 1969 (Box-folder Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Consumer Affairs - C & P Telephone - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1969 (Box-folder Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Consumer Affairs - VEPCO and Other Power Companies - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1969 (Box-folder Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Consumer Affairs - Location of Power Plants - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, 1969 (Box-folder Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Health and Welfare - Medical Center for Tidewater, 1969 (Box-folder Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Constitutional Revision - Beginning and End of Special Session of General Assembly, 1969 (Box-folder Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Constitutional Revision - Special Session; Miscellaneous Records of Senate and House Actions, 1969 (Box-folder Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Constitutional Revision - Special Session; Senate Joint Resolution #23 (Basic Package of Revisions), 1969 (Box-folder Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Constitutional Revision - Special Session; Amendments Introduced by Henry Howell, 1969 (Box-folder Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Constitutional Revision - Special Session; Recommendations of Commission on Constitutional Revision, 1969 (Box-folder Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Constitutional Revision - Special Session of General Assembly; Recommendations by Various Groups, 1969 (Box-folder Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Constitutional Revision - Special Session; Proposals re: Bill of Rights, 1969 (Box-folder Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Constitutional Revision - Special Session; Proposals re: Conservation - Natural Resources, 1969 (Box-folder Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Constitutional Revision - Special Session, Proposals re: Article IX (Corporations) and Consumer Protection, 1969 (Box-folder Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Constitutional Revision - Special Session; Proposals re: Education, 1969 (Box-folder Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Constitutional Revision - Special Session; Correspondence re: Educational Amendments, 1969 (Box-folder Box 147, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series F: General Assembly Session, Constitutional Revision 1969
    - Proposals re: Executive Branch, 1969 (Box-folder Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Proposals re: Franchise and Officers - General; Voting Age, 1969 (Box-folder Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Proposals re: Judiciary, 1969 (Box-folder Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Proposals re: Legislative Branch, 1969 (Box-folder Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Proposals re: Local Government, 1969 (Box-folder Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Proposals re: Schedule of New Constitution; Amending Process; Stylistic Changes; Lottery; Initiative, 1969 (Box-folder Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Proposals re: Funding of State Debt, 1969 (Box-folder Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Proposals re: Taxation, 1969 (Box-folder Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Proposals re: Taxation and Finance, 1969 (Box-folder Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence re: Taxation of Property, 1969 (Box-folder Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series G: General Assembly Session 1970-1971
    - General, January-February, 1970 (Box-folder Box 148, Folder 11)
    - General, March, 1970 (Box-folder Box 148, Folder 12)
    - General, April, 1970 (Box-folder Box 148, Folder 13)
    - General, May, 1970 (Box-folder Box 148, Folder 14)
    - General, June, 1970 (Box-folder Box 148, Folder 15)
    - General, July-August, 1970 (Box-folder Box 148, Folder 16)
    - General, September-November, 1970 (Box-folder Box 149, Folder 1)
    - General, December, 1970 (Box-folder Box 149, Folder 2)
    - General (Undated Materials), January-August, 1970 (Box-folder Box 149, Folder 3)
    - General - Miscellaneous Commonwealth Reports, 1970 (Box-folder Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Consumer Affairs - Correspondence, January-August, 1970 (Box-folder Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Consumer Affairs - Insurance Regulation Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, January-August, 1970 (Box-folder Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Consumer Affairs - Utilities Regulation Correspondence, January-August, 1970 (Box-folder Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Consumer Affairs - VEPCO (Consumer Complaints, etc.) - Correspondence, 1970 (Box-folder Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Education - Correspondence; Miscellaneous Material, January-August, 1970 (Box-folder Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Finances - Report of Comptroller for Fiscal Year 1970 (Box-folder Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Health and Welfare - Correspondence and Miscellaneous Material, January-August, 1970 (Box-folder Box 149, Folder 11)
    - Health and Welfare - Department of Health - Annual Report (1969), 1970 (Box-folder Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Nuclear Power Plants - VEPCO Argument before Atomic Energy Commission re: North Anna Stations 1 and 2, 1970 (Box-folder Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Nuclear Power Plants - VEPCO Applications for North Anna Stations 1 and 2; Miscellaneous Material, 1970 (Box-folder Box 150, Folder 3)
    - General, January 1-15, 1971 (Box-folder Box 150, Folder 4)
    - General, January 16-31, 1971 (Box-folder Box 150, Folder 5)
    - General, February 1-14, 1971 (Box-folder Box 150, Folder 6)
    - General, February 15-28, 1971 (Box-folder Box 150, Folder 7)
    - General, March 1-15, 1971 (Box-folder Box 150, Folder 8)
    - General, March 16-31, 1971 (Box-folder Box 150, Folder 9)
    - General, April 1-15, 1971 (Box-folder Box 150, Folder 10)
    - General, April 16-30, 1971 (Box-folder Box 150, Folder 11)
    - General, May 1-15, 1971 (Box-folder Box 151, Folder 1)
    - General, May 16-31, 1971 (Box-folder Box 151, Folder 2)
    - General, June, 1971 (Box-folder Box 151, Folder 3)
    - General, July-December, 1971 (Box-folder Box 151, Folder 4)
    - General - Miscellaneous Articles; Periodicals, 1971 (Box-folder Box 151, Folder 5)
    - General - V.J. Carlo - "U.S. in '76" - Part I (Legislative Program - Unsolicited), 1971 (Box-folder Box 151, Folder 6)
    - General - V.J. Carlo - "U.S. in '76" - Part II (Legislative Program - Unsolicited), 1971 (Box-folder Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Conservation - Dismal Swamp Preservation, January-June, 1971 (Box-folder Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Conservation - Wetlands Preservation, 1971 (Box-folder Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Consumer Affairs (General), 1971 (Box-folder Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Consumer Affairs - "Bank Cards and their Regulation," 1971 (Box-folder Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Consumer Affairs - Blue Cross/Blue Shield Correspondence, 1971 (Box-folder Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Consumer Affairs - Blue Cross/Blue Shield - Data and Testimony re: Virginia Structure, May-October, 1971 (Box-folder Box 151, Folder 13)
    - Consumer Affairs - Blue Cross/Blue Shield - Data and Testimony re: Virginia Structure, November-December, 1971 (Box-folder Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Consumer Affairs - Roanoke Valley Legal Aid Society - Consumer Legislation Package, 1971 (Box-folder Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Consumer Affairs - Insurance Companies, 1971 (Box-folder Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Consumer Affairs - Insurance Regulation; Report on "Revision of the Property and Casualty Insurance Ratemaking Process..." (S.C.C. Report), 1971 (Box-folder Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Consumer Affairs - Public Utilities Correspondence, 1971 (Box-folder Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Consumer Affairs - Public Utilities, Material re: Auditing Service, Inc., 1971 (Box-folder Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Education - Miscellaneous Reports - V.A.L.C. - Continuing Education; State Department of Education - Allocation of Funds; School Buses; Virginia Council of State College Presidents; State Student Financial Aid, 1971 (Box-folder Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Energy - Reports on Atomic Power, 1967-1971 (Box-folder Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Energy - Inter Technology Corporation: "The U.S. Energy Problem," Volume I; "Energy Conservation, Effluent Control..." 1971 (Box-folder Box 152, Folder 9)
    - General Assembly - Communication from Various Commissions, 1971 (Box-folder Box 152, Folder 10)
    - General Assembly - Miscellaneous Records of 1971 Session, January-June, 1971 (Box-folder Box 152, Folder 11)
    - General Assembly- Weekly Cumulative Index of Bills - Through January 13, 1971 (Box-folder Box 153, Folder 1)
    - General Assembly - Weekly Cumulative Index of Bills - Through January 20, 1971 (Box-folder Box 153, Folder 2)
    - General Assembly - Weekly Cumulative Index of Bills - Through January 27, 1971 (Box-folder Box 153, Folder 3)
    - General Assembly - Weekly Cumulative Index of Bills - Through February 3, 1971 (Box-folder Box 153, Folder 4)
    - General Assembly - Weekly Cumulative Index of Bills - Through February 17, 1971 (Box-folder Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Health and Welfare - Report on Fairfax Hospital, September, 1971 (Box-folder Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Health and Welfare - "Needs of the Handicapped" - A V.A.L.C. Report, October, 1971 (Box-folder Box 153, Folder 7)
    - Health and Welfare - "The Shortage of Family Physicians" - A V.A.L.C. Report, December, 1971 (Box-folder Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Health and Welfare - "Social Work Services" - A V.A.L.C. Report, November, 1971 (Box-folder Box 153, Folder 9)
    - Highways in Virginia - V.A.L.C. Reports, 1971 (Box-folder Box 153, Folder 10)
    - Highways: 1-64 Extension - Dr. Leonard Ravitz Material, January- June, 1971 (Box-folder Box 153, Folder 11)
    - Judicial System - Juries Report by Judicial Council, 1971 (Box-folder Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Land Use - "Laws Relating to Eminent Domain" - A V.A.L.C. Report, November, 1971 (Box-folder Box 153, Folder 13)
    - Legal Aid Society of Roanoke Valley - Miscellaneous Communications, 1971 (Box-folder Box 153, Folder 14)
    - Railroads: National Rail Passenger System (Amtrak), Miscellaneous Material, January-June, 1971 (Box-folder Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Reapportionment of Norfolk Senatorial Districts; Miscellaneous Material, January-June, 1971 (Box-folder Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Taxes - "Implementation of a Simplified Tax System for Virginia Taxpayers," 1971 (Box-folder Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council - Miscellaneous Reports and Other Communications, 1971 (Box-folder Box 154, Folder 4)
    - VEPCO - Award of Excellence from Electric Light & Power, November, 1971 (Box-folder Box 154, Folder 5)
    - V.A.L.C. Study Commission - Insurance Industry; General Correspondence, 1970 (Box-folder Box 154, Folder 6)
    - V.A.L.C. Study Commission - Insurance Industry Committee Correspondence, April-May, 1971 (Box-folder Box 154, Folder 7)
    - V.A.L.C. Study Commission - Insurance Industry; Committee Correspondence, June, 1971 (Box-folder Box 154, Folder 8)
    - V.A.L.C. Study Commission - Insurance Industry; Committee Correspondence, July, 1971 (Box-folder Box 154, Folder 9)
    - V.A.L.C. Study Commission - Insurance Industry; Committee Correspondence, August-September, 1971 (Box-folder Box 154, Folder 10)
    - V.A.L.C. Study Commission - Insurance Industry; Committee Correspondence, October, 1971 (Box-folder Box 154, Folder 11)
    - V.A.L.C. Study Commission - Insurance Industry; Howell Correspondence re: Commission, February-August, 1971 (Box-folder Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Statements by Insurance Companies, June 22, 1971 (Box-folder Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Statements by Insurance Agents, July 13, 1971 (Box-folder Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Testimony before Commission - Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box-folder Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Proposals re: Insurance Regulations - Miscellaneous, January-April, 1971 (Box-folder Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Material from Insurance Groups, 1971 (Box-folder Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Material from American Insurance Association, 1971 (Box-folder Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Material from American Insurance Association, 1971 (Box-folder Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Material from National Association of Independent Insurers, 1971 (Box-folder Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Material from Nationwide Insurance, 1971 (Box-folder Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Material re: Insurance Rules in California, Georgia, 1971 (Box-folder Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Material re: Insurance Rules in Massachusetts, Pennsylvania, 1971 (Box-folder Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Articles - Newsclippings re: Insurance, 1971 (Box-folder Box 155, Folder 12)
    - "Availability of Automobile Insurance in Virginia..." - Robert L. Brown (University of Richmond), 1971 (Box-folder Box 155, Folder 13)
    - "Reform of the Vehicle Liability Insurance Market" - G. R. Tyler and G. E. Hoffer (Virginia Commonwealth University), 1971 (Box-folder Box 155, Folder 14)
- SERIES V: LIEUTENANT GOVERNORSHIP 1971-1974
  - Sub-Series A: Inauguration
    - Planning, November-December, 1971 (Box-folder Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Lists of People to be Invited, November, 1971 (Box-folder Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Letters of Invitation - Printed Invitations, November, 1971 (Box-folder Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Replies to Invitations from General Public, November- December, 1971 (Box-folder Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Replies to Invitations from Public Figures, November 1971 (Box-folder Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Howell Inaugural Speech, December 4, 1971 (Box-folder Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Guest Book I, December 4, 1971 (Box-folder Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Guest Book II, December 4, 1971 (Box-folder Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Howell Thank-you Letters, December, 1971 (Box-folder Box 156, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series B: General Files